(Bernadette:)'cause I love
how things worked out.
(Howard:)Me, too.
(Howard:)And I think you're
even more beautiful
(Howard:)than this rose.
Wow. The last time
I saw my grandma,
(Penny:)the most exciting thing
was watching the ash
(Penny:)of her cigarette get longer
and wondering
(Penny:)if it was gonna fall
in her pudding.
(Leonard:)Did it?
(Penny:)Yeah, right in there.
(Penny:)She ate it and everything.
(knocking)
SHELDON: Leonard and Penny.
(Meemaw:)Leonard and Penny.
Leonard and Penny.
Come in!
LEONARD:
Hey. What happened?
(Leonard:)Is Amy gone?
(Sheldon:)No. They asked me to leave
(Sheldon:)so they could speak privately.
(Penny:)Uh-oh.
Yeah, I know. It was quite tense.
(Sheldon:)So here's
the million dollar question:
(Sheldon:)uh, who wants to pop over there
and get my trains?
(Penny:)All right.
I've made up my mind.
(Raj:)I'm gonna do the right thing,
call this girl,
(Raj:)and let her know
that I'm in a relationship.
(Howard:)Okay, so far we've heard,
“made up my mind,
I'm dumping Emily.”
“Made up my mind
to date both of them
(Bernadette:)by pretending
to be twin brothers.”